So a lot of people have been asking me, haha. Hey Killian
What did you think of E3 and things just because I review video games?
Doesn't mean I actually [liked] them the last video game
I really liked was Metroid prime pinball
And I highly doubt in 10 low is going to announce any more board related Metroid games
But I watched all the press conferences just because of your pressure and I have reviewed them
Bethesda okay, so first it showed some doom footage
But it wasn't a horror game way to betray your franchise then they announced dishonored 2 sadly
I have yet to play the first one
I mean, I've reviewed it. Haven't played it though rest of the conference was about fallout 4 [a] lot of people are excited
I'm not a lot of people keep telling me. [oh] fallout is great
You should check out follow [up], so I rented fallout tactics brotherhood of steel, and I just don't get it. I don't
See, it's just not for me. I'm giving this conference [online]
Microsoft hey
Do you guys remember when we reveal the Xbox one [our] market strategy is [sports] and fuck Europe could you please?
Forget guys the Microsoft press conference was ok they announced plants VS.. Zombies Garden Warfare 2 so that's fantastic?
But they also talked about a bunch of stuff that no one cares about 14, [ea] buncha lovable bastards as always
24 ubisoft they made many references to very funny maymays, and that gave me [a] grand love
but in the new Assassin's creed game you play as the assassins not the loveable team of ragtag heroes then again A
Templar cinematic wouldn't be very fun
it would just be some [guy] sitting in front of a desk getting things done and
Planning for retirement [a] bar fight is just more fun to watch
29 - 13 sony
Didn't watch it. But I read a YouTube comment
That said it was pretty good, so I'm giving it done 19 Nintendo like I said at the start
I [really] don't care about Nintendo. The only little game. I like is Metroid prime pinball sure Metroid prime was okay
Kind sure Kinda enjoyable, but it wasn't complete until they added the bomb. Oh look new prime game
I'm sure the fans must be really excited wait what?
What?
look
No
42 No 43
42 it's a good score. Let's not get ahead of ourselves
PC. There was a PC conference for the first time there was nothing [that] really interested me to be honest the crowd went wild when?
They showed the first official gameplay of Beyond good and evil 2 but I still haven't played the first one if you're interested in more
IIi
2015 content, you should probably check out another channel
And that is the kilian experience check out my parody reviews next [review] review is going to be silent Hill
Syusai Silent Hill 2 - cycle - damn it